<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Solvia</title>
    <link>https://solvia.co.za/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Solvia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-za</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 11:08:57 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://solvia.co.za/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flesh &amp; Bone</title>
      <link>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/flesh-bone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 11:08:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/flesh-bone/</guid>
      <description>Here there’s something moving Under flesh &amp; bone &amp; sky I know there’s something moving Under flesh and bone and sky Living I barely notice Barely see the world go by  I know that this can only Hurt but I won’t hate or cry Living I barely notice Barely see the world go by I know that this can only  Hurt but I won’t hate or cry  Flesh &amp; Bone is a meditation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free album download</title>
      <link>https://solvia.co.za//sedition//</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 11:07:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://solvia.co.za//sedition//</guid>
      <description>My only prayer Judas Nixon&#39;s nightmare Bilderberg hustle Deus infinitus Green eyes Sedition Flesh &amp; bone Solvia Divinorum - Full album</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sedition</title>
      <link>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/sedition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 11:07:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/sedition/</guid>
      <description>“I have sworn, upon the Altar of God, Eternal hostility, against every form of Tyranny over the mind of man” Thomas Jefferson We are the FIST of a people oppressed We are Liberty, Justice and war without rest No one can stop us the fools they have tried WE ARE ETERNAL REBELLION, ALL TYRANTS MUST DIE! We are eternal for we live in all of you We are the fire that burns in your mind When you feel tyranny pushing its boot on you That righteous anger is liberties pride DOMINATE CRUSH THOSE WHO DOMINATE RISE AND RESIST YOU MUST DESTROY AND CRUSH THOSE WHO DOMINATE YOU We are Anonymous We are Legion We do not forgive We do not forget We are under the dominance of Financial Treason We do not forgive We do not forget “I have sworn, upon the Altar of God, Eternal hostility against every form of Tyranny over the mind of man” Thomas Jefferson We are Anonymous We are Legion We do not forgive We do not forget We are under the dominance of Financial Treason We do not forgive We do not forget NO!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Eyes</title>
      <link>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/green-eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 11:06:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/green-eyes/</guid>
      <description>She is greed and She is envy Know her lust She’ll bleed you empty She’ll possess you You won’t notice She’ll obsess you You’ll lose focus Keep on smiling She won’t lose you Keep on smiling Like you used to That’s a good boy Don’t you question Insecure mental projection Come rest you look far too weary You’ve been crusading for far too long Come lay your head on the pillow I know that you’re only so strong There’s no trophy worth all this pain Yet you go back again and again There’s still time for you to let go She has needs and Now she needs you No one’s perfect Who could blame you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deus Infinitus</title>
      <link>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/deus-infinitus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 11:05:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/deus-infinitus/</guid>
      <description>Everyone must die someday No exceptions no one stays Let it be if I must go Leave this only world I know One last breath Fades to death But I’m not dead I’m just not breathing Now I fly Ten dimensional skies Consciousness A waking dream And I feel fine Outside time I’m alive I’m just not Breathing I see your eyes Crying lies You were Born to Cry YOU ARE Born innocent and PERFECT Divine in every ASPECT Your life a thread of This ETERNAL You can’t see me Though I still hear you From a space where living life Is just a dream SEE THERE Are more stars in THE SKY Than grains of sand ON EARTH We are  SENTIENT STAR DUST Everyone must die someday No exceptions no one stays Let it be if I must go Leave this only world I know Death is freedom death is kind Death will free me from my mind Unleash my mortality Once again a part of the(e) DEUS INFINITUS Breath in the air Nothings to fear Down by the Lake View the heavens so clear Just passing the time So little time So much there to live for So hard to see why DEATH COMES Relentless and UNCARING Ripping you from BEING No time or mind to Chain or hold you Once again I’m seeing This is glorious And it frees my soul Just to know THAT THERE Are more stars in THE SKY Than grains of sand ON EARTH We are SENTIENT STAR DUST DEUS INFINITUS  IM COMING HOME  The concept of “God” is all encompassing- there is nothing that is not “God”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bilderberg Hustle</title>
      <link>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/bilderberg-hustle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 11:04:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/bilderberg-hustle/</guid>
      <description>What have we done? What have we done? This government no longer serves everyone Only fat cats in office and all of their friends With their tenders and new cars and platinum rings It’s a goddamn shame How they’ve fallen from grace I see bribes and corruption all over the place And it’s blatant and glaring and thrown in our face It’s hard bearing witness to such a disgrace Silver tongue!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nixons Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/nixons-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 11:03:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/nixons-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>“We must wage total war against dangerous drugs” Richard Nixon A war is being waged on our personal freedom Control freaks deciding what we may or may not breathe in Every day, good people are put through hell Sentenced to waste years away locked in a cell -Addicts need help not persecution Locking them up is not a solution They say the war on drugs is about saving the kids  So they put them behind bars - Fucking Hypocrites!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judas</title>
      <link>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/judas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 11:02:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/judas/</guid>
      <description>Now that you’re here I think that we should have a talk You’ve been up to mischief again Those who carry secrets find their souls wearing thin Heavy you’ll struggle my friend How many times did you choose to bite your tongue? Then wretched in silence you spoke Ambitions of vengeance and whispers of hate Careful, I fear that you’ll choke We need to feel all of this pain from both sides No one is clean we have all sold lies I can’t face you I can’t speak Let me plot in shadow You make me weak All I want is What you’ve got But this righteous envy Has caused my soul to rot How many times did you choose to bite your tongue?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Only Prayer</title>
      <link>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/my-only-prayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 11:01:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://solvia.co.za/lyrics/my-only-prayer/</guid>
      <description>Oumikami, who is the Sun, once said In a language obscure unless you&#39;re dead Or dying each day (as so you should) That metal, fire, water, wind and wood And all concerns of a reptile&#39;s brain Are arrested, turned, and ingested through pain. Pain alone bears the wounded torch, Along pathways where (crosswise) soft sunflowers Scorch our flowering-hours. Never cease to bear Our quiet march, through sanity spare Abrade us into another age Sandblast our insides until We’re washed of indignant fear and rage And with forgiveness fill Amaterasu I pray you my Sun My flaring and only Omnipotent one Abrade us of anger Abrade us of pride Abrade us of fear Abrade us of self Why the hell Is everyone familiar?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>