<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lyrics on Solvia</title>
    <link>https://hisdisgrace.github.io/lyrics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lyrics on Solvia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 03:24:57 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hisdisgrace.github.io/lyrics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Judas</title>
      <link>https://hisdisgrace.github.io/lyrics/judas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 03:24:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hisdisgrace.github.io/lyrics/judas/</guid>
      <description>Now that you’re here I think that we should have a talk You’ve been up to mischief again Those who carry secrets find their souls wearing thin Heavy you’ll struggle my friend How many times did you choose to bite your tongue? Then wretched in silence you spoke Ambitions of vengeance and whispers of hate Careful, I fear that you’ll choke We need to feel all of this pain from both sides No one is clean we have all sold lies I can’t face you I can’t speak Let me plot in shadow You make me weak All I want is What you’ve got But this righteous envy Has caused my soul to rot How many times did you choose to bite your tongue?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Only Prayer</title>
      <link>https://hisdisgrace.github.io/lyrics/my-only-prayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 03:22:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hisdisgrace.github.io/lyrics/my-only-prayer/</guid>
      <description>Oumikami, who is the Sun, once said In a language obscure unless you&#39;re dead Or dying each day (as so you should) That metal, fire, water, wind and wood And all concerns of a reptile&#39;s brain Are arrested, turned, and ingested through pain. Pain alone bears the wounded torch, Along pathways where (crosswise) soft sunflowers Scorch our flowering-hours. Never cease to bear Our quiet march, through sanity spare Abrade us into another age Sandblast our insides until We’re washed of indignant fear and rage And with forgiveness fill Amaterasu I pray you my Sun My flaring and only Omnipotent one Abrade us of anger Abrade us of pride Abrade us of fear Abrade us of self Why the hell Is everyone familiar?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>